Society of Southwest Archivists records, Inclusive: 1970-2017, Bulk: 1973-1993, 2003-2016
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Committee Documents, 1972-2017, undated; 2
  - Executive Board, 1973-2017, undated; 1
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1991 October (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1992 February (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1992 February (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1992 June 4 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1992 June 6 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1992 June 6 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 4), 1992 November (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 4), 1992 November (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Literary: Minutes (3 of 4), 1992 November (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Literary: Minutes (4 of 4), 1992 November (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 3), 1993 March (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 3), 1993 March (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Literary: Minutes (3 of 3), 1993 March (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 3), 1993 May (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 3), 1993 May (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Literary: Minutes (3 of 3), 1993 May (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1993 October (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1993 October (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1994 February (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1994 February (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1996 May (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1996 August (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1996 September (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1997 February (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1997 May 29 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1997 May 31 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 1997 October (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 1997 October (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1999 February 19 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1999 May (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Minutes, 1999 October (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Minutes (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Literary: Minutes (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2003 January (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2003 May (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Minutes and Reports, 2003 October (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2004 February (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2004 May (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2004 October 7-8 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2005 May (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2005 October 17 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2006 February-July (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2006 December (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Minutes and Reports, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Minutes, 2012-2016 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Notes, 1974 September (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Notes (1 of 4), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Notes (2 of 4), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Notes (3 of 4), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Notes (4 of 4), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Notes (1 of 4), undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Literary: Notes (2 of 4), undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Literary: Notes (3 of 4), undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Notes (4 of 4), undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Notes: Logo, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Literary: Notes: Voting, 1988-1993 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Literary: Notes: Voting, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Literary: Notes: Voting, 1995-2000, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Officer Lists, 1975-1990, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Officer Profiles, 1993 March-April 16 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Officer Profiles, 1993 April 19-26 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Officer Profiles, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Officer and Committee Reports, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Officer and Committee Reports, 2014 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Officer and Committee Reports, 2015 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Officer and Committee Reports, 2016 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Reports, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Reports, 1979-1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Reports, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Reports, 2000-2001, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Reports, 2002-2005 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Reports, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Audio Cassette, 1973 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Audio Cassette: Board Meeting, 1981 May 8 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Digital Media: Jennifer Day: Secretary Files (2012-2016), Program Committee Chair (2017), Annual Meeting Guide Update (2017), and Procedures Manual Update (2017), 2012-2017 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - President, 1991-2013; 2
    - Leon Miller: Correspondence and Literary, 1999-2000 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Kathlene Ferris: Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Kathlene Ferris: Correspondence and Literary: Executive Board Meetings, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Kathlene Ferris: Correspondence and Literary: 32nd Annual Meeting, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence (1 of 2), 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence (2 of 2), 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence: Concerning Archivist of the United States Allen Weinstein, 2005 February (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence: Discussion Panel Proposal, 2004 July (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence: Gift Proposal for Kim Allen Scott, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence: National Historical Publications and Records Commission, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence: Thank You Notes After Annual Meeting, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence and Financial Documents: Society of American Archivists Mixer, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence and Literary: Executive Board Meeting: Arlington, Texas, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence and Reports: Advocacy Issues, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence and Rosters: New Members, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Shelly Kelly: Financial Documents, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Shelly Kelly: Invitations to Dedication of William J. Clinton Presidential Center, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Shelly Kelly: Report to Executive Board: "First Look at the A* Census Data", 2005 October 8 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Shelly Kelly: Sister M. Claude Lane Award (1 of 2), 1991-2005 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Shelly Kelly: Sister M. Claude Lane Award (2 of 2), 1991-2005 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Amanda Focke: Correspondence: General, 2012-2013 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Amanda Focke: Correspondence: Nominating Committee, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Amanda Focke: Correspondence and Literary: Local Arrangements Committee, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Amanda Focke: Literary: Agendas, Minutes, Notes, and Reports (1 of 2), 2012-2013 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Amanda Focke: Literary: Agendas, Minutes, Notes, and Reports (2 of 2), 2012-2013 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Amanda Focke: Literary: Local Arrangements Committee Planning, 2013 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Amanda Focke: Literary: Minutes: Finance Committee, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Amanda Focke: Literary: Notes and Reports: Wild Apricot Membership Management System, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Amanda Focke: Literary: Summit of Regional Organization and Society of American Archivists Leaders, 2012 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Vice President, 1984-2013; 3
    - Kent Keeth: Correspondence: Nomination, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Leon Miller: Correspondence and Literary, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Kathleen Ferris: Correspondence and Literary: Program Committee, 2002-2003 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence: Concerning Archivist of the United States Allen Weinstein, 2004 April (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence: Program Committee, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence: Program Committee, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence: Program Committee: Scheduling Sessions, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence and Notes: Program Committee: Early Ideas, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence and Session Proposals: Program Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Shelly Kelly: Literary: Program Committee: Report to Board, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Amanda Focke: Correspondence: Sister M. Claude Lane Award, 2011-2013 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Amanda Focke: Correspondence and Literary: Program Committee Chair, 2011-2012 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Amanda Focke: Literary: Agendas, Minutes, Notes, and Reports (1 of 2), 2011-2012 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Amanda Focke: Literary: Agendas, Minutes, Notes, and Reports (2 of 2), 2011-2012 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Amanda Focke: Literary: Meeting Evaluations: SSA and Conference of Inter-Mountain Archivists, 2012 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Treasurer, 1982-2010; 4
    - Financial Documents: Tax-Exempt, 1982-1997 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Gerianne Schaad: Correspondence (1 of 2), 2003-2006 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Gerianne Schaad: Correspondence (2 of 2), 2003-2006 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Gerrianne Schaad: Financial: Budgets and Reports, 2005-2010 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Gerianne Schaad: Literary: Reports, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Past President, 2006; 5
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence: Scholarships Committee, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Awards Committee, 1974-2014, undated; 6
    - Correspondence, 1974 September-November (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1974 December-1975 January (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1975 February-September (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1975 October-December (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1976 January 5-13 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1990 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 2001 January-March (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 2001 April 2 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 2001 April 3-2007 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 2007 May-2008 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Annual Meeting Scholarship, 2001 January-April (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Annual Meeting Scholarship, 2001 May, undated (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Distinguished Service Award, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: 2014 Distinguished Service Award, 2014 January (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: M. Claude Lane Award, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Legal: Resolution, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Literary: Award Nomination, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Literary: Annual Meeting Scholarship, circa 2001 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Certificate, 1975-1978, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Literary: General, 1990-2008, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Long-Range Committee, 1984-1992, undated; 7
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 April 5 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1989 April 10-1990 August (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1990 September-1991 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence and Survey, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Literary: Committee Policies (1 of 2), 1991 May (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Literary: Committee Policies (2 of 2), 1991 May (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Literary: Committee Policies, 1992 January (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Literary: Committee Policies, 1992 February (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Literary: General, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Program Committee, 1972-2017, undated; 8
    - Correspondence and Literary, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1976 July-September (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1976 October-November 18 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, 1976 November 29-December 7 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1976 December 8-26 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1977 January-February (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1977 March-April (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1977 March 20 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1977 May 20 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1979 January-February (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1979 April-December (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1994 January-April (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1994 April-May (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1994 April-May (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Literary: General, 2002-2012 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Literary: "Program Chair Handbook", 2017 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Sandra Myres: Corerspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Sandra Myres: Correspondence and Notes, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Kathlene Ferris: Correspondence and Literary: Session Proposals, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Shelly Kelly: Correspondence: Vote on Program Sessions, 2003-2004 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Shelly Kelly: Literary: Newsletter and Website Submissions, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Survey Committee, undated; 9
    - Literary: Surveys (1 of 7), undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Literary: Surveys (2 of 7), undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Literary: Surveys (3 of 7), undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Literary: Surveys (4 of 7), undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Literary: Surveys (5 of 7), undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Literary: Surveys (6 of 7), undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Surveys (7 of 7), undated (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Site Committee, 1974-2000, undated; 10
    - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1976 January-May (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1976 October-1977 May (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1977 June-December (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1978 January (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1978 September-1979 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1984 July (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1984 August-September (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1984 October-1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1990 May (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1990 June-September (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1990 October-1999, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Fayetteville Proposal, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Fort Worth Proposal, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Literary: General, 1989, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Reports, 1976-1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Survey Results, 1997-1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Ad Hoc Committee, 1974-2017, undated; 11
    - Correspondence, 1974-1975 April 24 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1975 April 24 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1975 April 28-May 9 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1975 May 12-16 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1975 May 19-27 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1975 May 29-June (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1975 July-October (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1975 November (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1975 December 1-12 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1975 December 17-1976 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1989, undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Goals and Objectives, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence and Reports: Goals and Objectives, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: SSA Policy Book, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Literary: Draft: "Annual Meeting Guide", 2017 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Literary: Drafts of "Committee and Procedures Manual", 2005 May-October (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Literary: Dues Restructuring, 2005-2010 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Literary: General, 1985, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Notes, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Literary: "Officer and Committee Procedures Manual", 2017 May (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Report, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Report, circa 1976 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Reports: Notes, circa 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Responses to Reports (1 of 2), 1976 April (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Responses to Reports (2 of 2), 1976 April (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Suggested Projects, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: Arizona, circa 1993 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: Arkansas, circa 1993 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: "Directories: Master", circa 1993 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 11)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: Index, circa 1993 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 12)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: Intro, 1993 September 30 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 13)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: "Intro, New", circa 1993 (Box 45 OVZ, Folder 14)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: "Last Update", 1993 April 18 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 1)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: Louisiana, circa 1993 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 2)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: "Louisiana, Additions Included", 1992 August 31 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 3)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: "Master", 1993 November 23 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: State-By-State, circa 1993 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: "Texas A-G" (1 of 3), circa 1993 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 6)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: "Texas A-G" (2 of 3), circa 1993 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 7)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: "Texas A-G" (3 of 3), circa 1993 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 8)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: "Texas H-Z", circa 1993 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 9)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: Word Perfect 5.1, circa 1993 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 10)
    - Digital Media: SSA Directory: "Word Perfect 5.1: New Mexico Entries", circa 1993 (Box 46 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Scholarships Committee, 1982-2015, undated; 12
    - Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1985 January (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1985 January (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1985 April (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1985 April (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1985 May-September (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1986 February-April 16 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1986 April 21 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1986 April 21 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 January (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1987 February-March (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1987 March 18 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1987 March 18 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1987 May-August (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1988 April 4 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1988 April 4 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1989 July (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1989 July (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1989 September-1990 February (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence (1 of 2), 1990 April (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence (2 of 2), 1990 April (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1990 May-1991 January (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1991 February-March (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1991 March (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1991 May-1992 April (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1992 May-1998 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2012 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 1986-1991 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 1998-2001 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and Applications, 2011-2012 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and Applications, 2012-2013 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and Literary: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 1984-1992 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence and Literary: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship (1 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence and Literary: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship (2 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and Literary: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship (3 of 3), 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence and Literary: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Agendas and Minutes: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 1999-2002 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Literary: Applications: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Literary: Applications: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Literary: Applications: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 1999-2001 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Literary: Applications: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Literary: Candidate Selection, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Literary: Candidate Selection (1 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Literary: Candidate Selection (2 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Literary: Candidate Selection (1 of 2), 1990-1994 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Literary: Candidate Selection (2 of 2), 1990-1994 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Literary: Fliers, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Literary: Fliers, 2014-2015 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Literary: General, 1997-1999, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Literary: General: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 1998-2003 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Literary: Promotional Materials, 2005-2006 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Literary: Reports: Otis Hebert, Jr. Scholarship, 2000-2002 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Local Arrangements Committee, 1984-2013, undated; 13
    - Correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 September 6 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1989 September 22-November 14 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1989 November 20-1990 March (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1990 June-December (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 January (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1994 February-May (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1994 August-1996 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1998 October-November (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1998 December-1999 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1999-2004 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 2005-2007 September (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 2007 October-2008, undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Edward Oetting, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Shelly Kelly, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Kay Bost, 2004-2007 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and Literary, 2005-2006 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Financial: Catering, 2007 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Financial: General, 1988, undated (Box 27, Folder 11)